{
    "id": "6a63fffec6bb46e58883bae4bed4e239",
    "title": "Degree modifiers exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "8c2b31b1e5814a9bb9f45e590cbd5cdc",
            "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "There is too ………………….noise in the street.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "How ………………….. people do you want to help you?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "They do …………………. a lot of business in the Middle East.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "quite"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He speaks ………………… a few languages.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "very",
                        "quite",
                        "rather"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "There are …………………. too many weapons in the world.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "far",
                        "quite",
                        "very"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "………………… of philosophy is concerned with questions nobody can answer.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Much",
                        "Many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "…………………. of the city was without electricity last night.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "Most",
                        "Much"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "We have bought too …………………. butter.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "much",
                        "many"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I think you have made …………………. a lot of mistakes.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "far",
                        "very",
                        "rather"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "This weather …………………. gets on my nerves.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "kind of",
                        "kinds of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}